<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Super Bowl LVIII</title>
	<atom:link href="https://li.fvtc.edu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://li.fvtc.edu/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 11:55:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Officials Will Hold Super Bowl at Full Capacity</title>
		<link>https://li.fvtc.edu/officials-will-hold-super-bowl-at-full-capacity/</link>
					<comments>https://li.fvtc.edu/officials-will-hold-super-bowl-at-full-capacity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 11:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://li.fvtc.edu/?p=36</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The Super Bowl will be sold out, according to officials in Los Angeles County. At the Super Bowl next month, the NFL most likely won’t need cardboard cutouts to fill the stands. COVID-19 infection rates are growing in the neighborhood and over the country due to the Omicron variant epidemic, but LA County does not ... <a title="Officials Will Hold Super Bowl at Full Capacity" class="read-more" href="https://li.fvtc.edu/officials-will-hold-super-bowl-at-full-capacity/" aria-label="More on Officials Will Hold Super Bowl at Full Capacity">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu/officials-will-hold-super-bowl-at-full-capacity/">Officials Will Hold Super Bowl at Full Capacity</a> appeared first on <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu">Super Bowl LVIII</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Super Bowl will be sold out, according to officials in Los Angeles County.</p>
<p>At the Super Bowl next month, the NFL most likely won’t need cardboard cutouts to fill the stands.</p>
<p>COVID-19 infection rates are growing in the neighborhood and over the country due to the Omicron variant epidemic, but LA County does not anticipate to restrict sports attendance.</p>
<p>Yahoo Sports was notified on Thursday by the Los Angeles County Department of Public Health that it is working closely with the NFL to host the Super Bowl. “We don’t expect capacity concerns during athletic events,” the group said, despite the uncertain future.</p>
<p>Los Angeles County and the NFL have both committed to look at other options if SoFi Stadium cannot host the Super Bowl as planned. WFAA reported Wednesday that the Dallas Cowboys’ AT&amp;T Stadium was contacted.</p>
<p>In reply to the pandemic, the NFL underlined that it still aims to hold the Super Bowl in Los Angeles and that it studies prospective backup venues every year. This state has stricter COVID-19 rules, and the Los Angeles County administration has been known to add additional limitations on a regular basis.</p>
<p>Sofi Stadium is expecting a capacity crowd of at least 70,000 people for the Super Bowl next month.</p>
<p>An indoor masks rule in California has been extended until February 15th, two days after the Super Bowl, by the state of California. In Los Angeles County, public gatherings with more than 10,000 attendees already mandate the use of face masks.</p>
<p>Although the Los Angeles Rams and Los Angeles Chargers have played all season at SoFi Stadium, both clubs have taken extra precautions related to the current viral spike. A negative COVID-19 test or evidence of vaccination is needed for all spectators over the age of five who desire to enter the stadium.</p>
<p>Last Super Bowl in Los Angeles: 1993. Although SoFi Stadium has not yet been completed when it got the NFL’s Super Bowl proposal in 2016, building has already begun.</p>
<p>Late last week, Yahoo Sports asked the California Department of Public Health how bad the Omicron illness had to grow before COVID-19 limitations were enforced. A commitment to hosting the Super Bowl in Los Angeles was made public on Wednesday by California Department of Health and Human Services Secretary <a href="https://board.coveredca.com/board-members/dr-mark-ghaly/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Dr. Mark Ghaly</a>.</p>
<p>Despite the global spike in COVID-19, the SoFi Stadium in Inglewood, California, is expected to be sold out for Super Bowl LVI on February 13.</p>
<p>To host the Super Bowl, the Los Angeles County Department of Public Health released a statement to Yahoo Sports. He went on to remark that in the future, “we do not foresee capacity limitations at athletic events”.</p>
<p>SoFi Stadium can hold up to 100,000 fans for important events like the Super Bowl.</p>
<p>On Wednesday, WFAA reported that the NFL was examining AT&amp;T Stadium in Arlington, Texas, as a backup Super Bowl location if local COVID regulations barred SoFi Stadium from hosting the game.</p>
<p>“The league did ask about a date,” a Cowboys insider told Leslie. “However, that is the sole instance of such in my research. There is a possibility that they are prepared for the worst possible outcome.”</p>
<p>According to NFL VP of Communications Brian McCarthy, the league is routinely reviewing backup plans:</p>
<p>“SoFi Stadium is set to host Super Bowl LVI on Sunday, February 13th. We have contacted many teams to enquire about stadium availability in the event that we cannot play the Super Bowl as scheduled due to weather-related difficulties or unanticipated incidents. This year’s Super Bowl will be held in Los Angeles, capping off another memorable NFL season for local fans and teams.”</p>
<p>Dr. Mark Ghaly, secretary of the California Department of Health and Human Services, says the Super Bowl is coming to Los Angeles.</p>
<p>All evidence lead to the Super Bowl being hosted in Los Angeles as scheduled.</p>
<p>Due of the epidemic, barely 25,000 people attended last year’s Super Bowl in Tampa, Florida.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu/officials-will-hold-super-bowl-at-full-capacity/">Officials Will Hold Super Bowl at Full Capacity</a> appeared first on <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu">Super Bowl LVIII</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://li.fvtc.edu/officials-will-hold-super-bowl-at-full-capacity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NFL Playoff Schedule 2024: Date, Time, TV Channel, Live Stream</title>
		<link>https://li.fvtc.edu/nfl-playoff-schedule-2024-date-time-tv-channel-live-stream/</link>
					<comments>https://li.fvtc.edu/nfl-playoff-schedule-2024-date-time-tv-channel-live-stream/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 11:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://li.fvtc.edu/?p=33</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The 2024 NFL Playoffs will start on Saturday, January 13, and end with the Super Bowl on Sunday, February 11, 2024. NFL Playoffs 2024 is going to be more competitive this year. Here’s everything you need to know about the NFL Playoffs schedule: kick-off time, TV Channel, score, and more. 2024 NFL Playoffs &#38; Key ... <a title="NFL Playoff Schedule 2024: Date, Time, TV Channel, Live Stream" class="read-more" href="https://li.fvtc.edu/nfl-playoff-schedule-2024-date-time-tv-channel-live-stream/" aria-label="More on NFL Playoff Schedule 2024: Date, Time, TV Channel, Live Stream">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu/nfl-playoff-schedule-2024-date-time-tv-channel-live-stream/">NFL Playoff Schedule 2024: Date, Time, TV Channel, Live Stream</a> appeared first on <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu">Super Bowl LVIII</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The 2024 NFL Playoffs will start on Saturday, January 13, and end with the Super Bowl on Sunday, February 11, 2024.</p>
<p>NFL Playoffs 2024 is going to be more competitive this year. Here’s everything you need to know about the NFL Playoffs schedule: kick-off time, TV Channel, score, and more.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>2024 NFL Playoffs &amp; Key Dates</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><strong>Wild-card games:</strong> January 13-15<br />
<strong>Divisional games:</strong> January 20-21<br />
<strong>Conference championships:</strong> January 28<br />
<strong>Pro Bowl:</strong> Sunday, February 4, 2024<br />
<strong>Super Bowl LVII:</strong> Sunday, February 11, 2024</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">When do the NFL playoffs start in 2024?</h2>
<p>The 2023-24 NFL playoffs race will begin on Saturday, January 13, 2024, and conclude on Sunday, January 29 with Conference championship games.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">NFL Playoff Wild-Card Round</h2>
<p>The NFL Wild Card round will kick off on Saturday, January 13 and ends on Monday, January 15. Fourteen teams participate in this stage; only the top 4 will attend the Divisional Round from each conference.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table is-style-stripes">
<table class="has-black-color has-electric-grass-gradient-background has-text-color has-background">
<thead>
<tr>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Date</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Matchup</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Time (ET)</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TV Channel</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Score</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Saturday, January 13</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">AFC: No. 4 vs. No. 5</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">4:30 PM</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">NBC/Peacock</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">–</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Saturday, January 13</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">AFC: No. 3 vs. No. 6</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">8:15 PM</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Peacock</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">–</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Sunday, January 14</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">NFC: No. 2 vs. No. 7</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">1:00 PM</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">CBS or FOX</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">–</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Sunday, January 14</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">NFC: No. 3 vs. No. 6</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">4:30 PM</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">CBS</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">–</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Sunday, January 14</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">AFC: No. 2 vs. No. 7</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">8:15 PM</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">NBC</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">–</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Monday, January 15</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">NFC: No. 4 vs. No. 5</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">8:00 PM</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">ESPN/ABC</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">–</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Divisional Round</h2>
<p>NFL Divisional round Playoff games kick off on Saturday, January 20 and end on Sunday, January 21. 8 teams go to the race and we get 4 top scorer teams from AFC and NFC Divisional rounds.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table is-style-stripes">
<table class="has-black-color has-electric-grass-gradient-background has-text-color has-background">
<thead>
<tr>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Date</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Matchup</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Time (ET)</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TV Channel</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Saturday, January 20</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">AFC: Winner of 4/5 vs. No. 1 seed</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TBA</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TBA</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Saturday, January 20</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">NFC: Winner of 4/5 vs. No. 1 seed</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TBA</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TBA</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Sunday, January 21</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">AFC: Winner of No. 2/7 vs. No. 3/6</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TBA</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TBA</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Sunday, January 21</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">NFC: Winner of No. 2/7 vs. No. 3/6</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TBA</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TBA</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conference championships</h2>
<p>The top 4 teams are playing AFC and NFC Championship games. The Conference championships winner to play Super Bowl, and the losing team will play in the pro bowl 2024.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table is-style-stripes">
<table class="has-black-color has-electric-grass-gradient-background has-text-color has-background">
<thead>
<tr>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Date</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Matchup</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Time (ET)</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TV</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Sunday, January 28</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">NFC Championship</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">3:00 PM</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">CBS</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Sunday, January 28</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">AFC Championship</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">6:30 PM</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">FOX</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How do I watch NFL playoff games on TV or live stream them online?</h2>
<p>Postseason play begins after the NFL regular season ends. This guide will show you how to watch all the NFL playoff games without paying for cable.</p>
<p>The best NFL Playoff Streaming Service allows you to watch playoff games on CBS, Fox, ABC, NBC, and ESPN. You’ll get a full refund if you cancel within 7 days of signing up with <a href="https://www.fubo.tv/stream/nfl/?irad=356362&amp;irmp=413786&amp;subId1=sbtime" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener sponsored nofollow">FuboTV</a>.</p>
<p>We will show you how to watch every NFL playoff game for free in 2024 during wild card weekend. If you don’t want to pay for Nickelodeon’s simulcast of one game, you may watch the playoffs for free on the following networks: CBS, FOX, ABC, NBC, and ESPN. Each service is compatible with Roku, Apple TV, Chromecast, iOS, and Android platforms.</p>
<p>As mentioned, reserving the option to watch NFL playoff games is easy.</p>
<p>You only need to focus on using the services that include the abovementioned channels. Besides FuboTV you could also use other top-rated services like Directv Stream, YouTube TV, Paramount+, Sling TV, and Hulu with Live TV.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Where is the NFL Pro Bowl 2024?</h2>
<p>The 2024 NFL Pro Bowl game will take place on Sunday, February 4, at Allegiant Stadium in Las Vegas. NFL all-star game will be shown on ESPN, ABC, and Disney XD and kick off at 3 pm ET/12 pm PT.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">When and where is Super Bowl 58 in 2024?</h2>
<p>Super Bowl 2024 will take place on Sunday, February 11, at 6:30 pm ET. The location is Allegiant Stadium in Paradise, Nevada. So, those who haven’t attended the stadium could reclaim their seat for the next Super Bowl.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table">
<table class="has-nv-dark-bg-color has-text-color has-background">
<thead>
<tr>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center"><strong>Matchup</strong></th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center"><strong>Start time</strong></th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">TV</th>
<th class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center"><strong>Live stream</strong></th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Super Bowl 58</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">6:30 p.m. ET</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">CBS</td>
<td class="has-text-align-center" data-align="center">Follow this Guide</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">What is the NFL playoff format &amp; How does it Work?</h2>
<p>Single-elimination playoffs are held following the regular season in the NFL. Each conference currently has seven teams in the playoffs. Breaking connections can be done in a certain way.</p>
<p>The NFL Playoffs include 14 teams. The NFL Playoff Bracket has seven teams from the American Football Conference and seven from the National Football Conference. Each conference has four divisions, and the top two teams from each division advance to the playoffs. Teams will be seeded 1–4, depending on their record. (1 seed) has the best record and has the advantage of playing at home. When it comes to conference tournaments, only the top two seeds receive a first-round bye.</p>
<p>The Wild Card Round will include the top three teams from each division. The best wild card team faces the fourth-seeded club from the division winner’s conference. They will be seeded 7th and 6th, meeting the division winners’ 2nd and 3rd seeds. Each league has three wild card teams.</p>
<p>The NCAA Tournament and the NBA Playoffs have “real” brackets, while the NFL does not. In a “true” bracket, the team that wins each game advances to the next round. In the second round of the NFL playoffs, the highest seed in each conference matches the lowest seed left in that conference.</p>
<p>Unless you remove the bracket, it will remain there. Here’s an example of a second-round shuffle in an NFL playoff bracket.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu/nfl-playoff-schedule-2024-date-time-tv-channel-live-stream/">NFL Playoff Schedule 2024: Date, Time, TV Channel, Live Stream</a> appeared first on <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu">Super Bowl LVIII</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://li.fvtc.edu/nfl-playoff-schedule-2024-date-time-tv-channel-live-stream/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What Time Does SuperBowl LVIII Kick off &#124; USA, UK, Canada, Italy &#038; Mexico</title>
		<link>https://li.fvtc.edu/what-time-does-superbowl-lviii-kick-off/</link>
					<comments>https://li.fvtc.edu/what-time-does-superbowl-lviii-kick-off/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 11:44:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://li.fvtc.edu/?p=12</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here are the kickoff times for Super Bowl LVIII in various countries: USA (Eastern Time): The kickoff time is 6:30 PM EST. UK (GMT): The kickoff time is 11:30 PM GMT. Canada (Eastern Time): The kickoff time is 6:30 PM EST. Italy (CET): The kickoff time is 12:30 AM CET (next day). Mexico (Central Time): ... <a title="What Time Does SuperBowl LVIII Kick off &#124; USA, UK, Canada, Italy &#038; Mexico" class="read-more" href="https://li.fvtc.edu/what-time-does-superbowl-lviii-kick-off/" aria-label="More on What Time Does SuperBowl LVIII Kick off &#124; USA, UK, Canada, Italy &#038; Mexico">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu/what-time-does-superbowl-lviii-kick-off/">What Time Does SuperBowl LVIII Kick off | USA, UK, Canada, Italy &#038; Mexico</a> appeared first on <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu">Super Bowl LVIII</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here are the kickoff times for Super Bowl LVIII in various countries:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>USA (Eastern Time):</strong> The kickoff time is 6:30 PM EST.</li>
<li><strong>UK (GMT):</strong> The kickoff time is 11:30 PM GMT.</li>
<li><strong>Canada (Eastern Time):</strong> The kickoff time is 6:30 PM EST.</li>
<li><strong>Italy (CET):</strong> The kickoff time is 12:30 AM CET (next day).</li>
<li><strong>Mexico (Central Time):</strong> The kickoff time is 5:30 PM CST.</li>
</ul>
<p>Please note that these times are approximate and may vary slightly based on the exact location within each country and any broadcast delays. Be sure to check local listings and official NFL sources for the most accurate kickoff time information.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu/what-time-does-superbowl-lviii-kick-off/">What Time Does SuperBowl LVIII Kick off | USA, UK, Canada, Italy &#038; Mexico</a> appeared first on <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu">Super Bowl LVIII</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://li.fvtc.edu/what-time-does-superbowl-lviii-kick-off/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How To Watch Super Bowl 2024 Live NFL Sunday Game</title>
		<link>https://li.fvtc.edu/how-to-watch-super-bowl-2024-live-nfl-sunday-game/</link>
					<comments>https://li.fvtc.edu/how-to-watch-super-bowl-2024-live-nfl-sunday-game/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 11:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://li.fvtc.edu/?p=8</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Super bowl is most awaited NFL game. If you are among fans searching for, how to watch Super bowl 2024 live online, you hit the bull’s eye.  Super Bowl LVIII will be watched by more than 6 million people on various streaming services. Among so many options to stream Super Bowl LVIII, this guide will tell you ... <a title="How To Watch Super Bowl 2024 Live NFL Sunday Game" class="read-more" href="https://li.fvtc.edu/how-to-watch-super-bowl-2024-live-nfl-sunday-game/" aria-label="More on How To Watch Super Bowl 2024 Live NFL Sunday Game">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu/how-to-watch-super-bowl-2024-live-nfl-sunday-game/">How To Watch Super Bowl 2024 Live NFL Sunday Game</a> appeared first on <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu">Super Bowl LVIII</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Super bowl is most awaited NFL game. If you are among fans searching for, how to <strong>watch Super bowl 2024 live online</strong>, you hit the bull’s eye.  Super Bowl LVIII will be watched by more than 6 million people on various streaming services. Among so many options to <strong><mark class="has-inline-color has-accent-color">stream Super Bowl LVIII</mark></strong>, this guide will tell you about best option to <strong>watch Super bowl 2024 on Tv</strong>. You can watch <strong>Super bowl game</strong> <strong>online</strong> on streaming service Hulu, Fubo Tv, Sling Tv, Peacock Tv &amp; on DAZN.</p>
<p>Streaming options depend on country where you live. We will explore cheapest option to watch Super Bowl LVIII, what OTT platform you need to choose &amp; on what Tv channels <strong>Super Bowl game 2024</strong> will be on? <strong>Fox Sports, CBS Sports, TSN, BBC &amp; Channel 7</strong> each will broadcast Super bowl LVIII in different countries. You can access any network you want on your Smart tv, Xbox, laptop &amp; on mobile. We have made it easy to stream Super bowl either you are outside USA or in America.</p>
<p>This year NFL promises to be something different. In Last year NFL earned $8.1 billion last year &amp; this year NFL going to surpass those figures as expected.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table is-style-stripes">
<table>
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>NFL Game</strong></td>
<td><strong>Super bowl LVIII</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Venue</strong></td>
<td>Allegiant Stadium, Paradise, Nevada</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Super bowl 2024 Kick off time</strong></td>
<td>6:30 P.M EST</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Super bowl 2024 Date</strong></td>
<td>11th Feb, 2024</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Teams</strong></td>
<td>TBD</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><strong>Channels</strong></td>
<td>CBS Sports, ESPN, Fox Sports</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>What time Super Bowl 2024 will Kick Off</strong></h2>
<p class="has-contrast-color has-text-color"><strong>Super bowl 2024</strong> is going to held in Las Vegas, Nevada. As there are 7 different time zones in USA, to know <strong>when Super Bowl 2024 will kick off</strong> in Alaska or West Coast or any other region we have complied timetable for <strong>NFL Super bowl fans</strong>. Super bowl LVIII will kick off on 11<sup>th</sup> Feb, 2024. If you are from Canada or Europe &amp; want to know<mark class="has-inline-color"> </mark><strong><mark class="has-inline-color has-accent-color">Super Bowl Kick off time</mark></strong> from Europe or Canada , you check this blog:</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table is-style-stripes">
<table class="has-very-light-gray-to-cyan-bluish-gray-gradient-background has-background">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>USA Time Zone</strong></td>
<td><strong> Super Bowl Kick off Time</strong></td>
<td><strong>Eastern Time</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Hawaii</td>
<td>1:30 P.M. HST</td>
<td>6:30 P.M. ET</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Alaska</td>
<td>2:30 P.M. AKDT</td>
<td>6:30 P.M. ET</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>West Coast</td>
<td>3:30 P.M. PT</td>
<td>6:30 P.M. ET</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Mountain time</td>
<td>4:30 P.M. MT</td>
<td>6:30 P.M. ET</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Midwest</td>
<td>5:30 P.M. CT</td>
<td>6:30 P.M. ET</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>East Coast</td>
<td>6:30 P.M. ET</td>
<td>6:30 P.M. ET</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Stream Super Bowl 2024 on Cable Tv:</strong></h2>
<p>You cannot compare anything with Television if you want to get better of <strong>NFL Super Bowl 2024 streaming</strong>. With Cable Service you can watch Super Bowl LVIII Online in USA. Cable Service allow you to access channels broadcasting NFL Super Bowl 2024 like <strong>CBS Sports, Nickelodeon, Fox Sports, ESPN &amp; BBC</strong>. Trustworthy cable service providers are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Cox</li>
<li>Spectrum</li>
<li>Xfinity</li>
<li>Optimum</li>
</ul>
<p>If you don’t have cable connection, you can get any of 1 mention below. We have provided the cost comparison of Cable service providers to make it easy for you to select. Just buy the connection &amp; Stream Super bowl at home. As <strong>Super bowl LVIII</strong> will be on Sunday, you can <strong>watch Super Bowl on tv channels</strong> with below Cable service providers.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table is-style-stripes">
<table class="has-light-green-cyan-background-color has-background">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Cable Service</strong></td>
<td><strong>Price</strong></td>
<td><strong>CBS</strong></td>
<td><strong>Nickelodeon</strong></td>
<td><strong>Univision<sup>†</sup></strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Cox</td>
<td>$56.00–$139.00/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Optimum</td>
<td>$35.00–$115.00/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Spectrum</td>
<td>$59.99/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Xfinity</td>
<td>$20.00–$80.00/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<p>Cable service is kind of expensive option, let’s explore streaming services to <strong>watch Super Bowl 2024 online</strong> live in one go.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Streaming Services to watch Live Super Bowl 2024</strong></h2>
<p>NFL is transmitting on famous and easily available channels all over the world. But in case no cable channels are available there can be different options to watch and enjoy NFL games. Following options can be availed in case of non-availability of cable.</p>
<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-layout-2 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button has-custom-font-size has-medium-font-size"><strong><mark class="has-inline-color has-base-3-color">Get EXPRESS VPN To Watch NFL Live<br />
(49% off + 3 Months Free)<br />
Offering Free Trial</mark></strong></div>
</div>
<p>NFL has launched its streaming service to stream NFL Live in 2022 where you can <strong>live stream Super Bowl 2024</strong>, pre-season games &amp; regular season in just <strong>$6.99/month.</strong> If you want to watch recaps &amp; NFL redzone, subscription will cost <strong>$14.99/Month</strong>. NFL+ to stream Super bowl offers 7 days free trial which can be cancel any time. If you cancel subscription before trial ends, it will let you <strong>watch free NFL Super Bowl 2024</strong>. That’s one of trick but don’t disclose anywhere else <strong><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/1f609.svg" alt="&#x1f609;" /></strong></p>
<p>YouTube recently won the streaming rights of NFL. Amazon has also righted to <strong>stream NFL Thursday night stream</strong>. Let’s discuss each option in detail.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table is-style-stripes">
<table class="has-light-green-cyan-background-color has-background">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Streaming Service</strong></td>
<td><strong>Price</strong></td>
<td><strong>CBS</strong></td>
<td><strong>Nickelodeon</strong></td>
<td><strong>Univision</strong><strong><sup>†</sup></strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>fuboTV</td>
<td>$74.99–$94.99/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" />*</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Hulu + Live TV</td>
<td>$69.99–$82.99/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td>—</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Philo</td>
<td>$25.00/mo.</td>
<td>—</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td>—</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Sling TV</td>
<td>$40.00–$55.00/mo.</td>
<td>—</td>
<td>—</td>
<td>—</td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>Vidgo</td>
<td>$69.99–$99.99/mo.</td>
<td>—</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>YouTube TV</td>
<td>$72.99/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Super bowl Live on YouTube TV: </strong></h3>
<p>YouTube TV is a streaming service from YouTube providing 100+ tv channels &amp; sports network. You can easily <strong>watch Sunday Super Bowl Live</strong> with YouTube base plan. It costs around <strong>$72.99/month. </strong>YouTube tv also offering <strong>Sunday night ticket to watch NFL games</strong> held afternoon. NFL Sunday ticket is add-on with YouTube Tv, you must have base plan to avail Sunday ticket.</p>
<p>You don’t need NFL Sunday ticket to <strong>stream Super Bowl LVIII</strong>. It is basically to watch NFL games which are not telecasting in your local area. If you are New York jets fan in Tennessee, you need Sunday ticket to watch NFL Game which is not streamed by CBS Sports, Fox or ESPN. As Super bowl will be broadcasted by all Tv channels, you can <strong>watch Super bowl with YouTube</strong> base plan.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Super Bowl LVIII on Sling TV: </strong></h3>
<p>Sling TV gives you interesting deals to <strong>watch Super bowl 2024 on Sling TV</strong> live, it splits Live NFL options in two choices. First option is named as Blue plan, it costs for <strong>$40/month</strong> and the other choice is called as Orange Plan for $40. You can also get Sling Orange + Blue in $55.</p>
<p>Sling Blue entertains the viewers on Thursday and Sunday on Fox, NBC and NFL Network. While Sling Orange telecast the games on Monday night on <strong>ESPN</strong>. And if you want to avail <strong>NFL RedZone</strong>, you need to choose Sling Blue.</p>
<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-layout-3 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button has-custom-font-size has-medium-font-size"><strong><mark class="has-inline-color has-base-3-color">Get EXPRESS VPN To Watch NFL Live<br />
(49% off + 3 Months Free)<br />
Offering Free Trial</mark></strong></div>
</div>
<p>Subscribers can add extra sports package by paying extra <strong>$10</strong> a month. Here the fans have to take a tough decision, and the smart offer motivates the users to buy the discount offer and enjoy the game. Sling TV does not provide CBS transmission, which telecast the matches on Sunday afternoons. Sling tv offers Fox, NBC &amp; NFL Network to watch Super bowl on Sunday.</p>
<p><strong>CBS All Access</strong> costs only <strong>$5.99/month</strong>. You need to pay only for four months to go through the NFL season. And four months of CBS All Access will take you through the NFL season, letting you <strong>watch NFL Games on Sunday</strong> afternoons. It makes for a good add-on for Sling TV subscribers.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Hulu with Live TV:</strong></h3>
<p>NFL Redzone on Hulu comes up as an add on to <strong>watch Super Bowl 2024 on Hulu</strong>. You must need a base Hulu plan that comes with add at cost of <strong>$49.99 for 3 months</strong>, on base plan one should buy sports add-on at <strong>$9.99/month</strong>.  Hulu is offering Disney+ &amp; ESPN+ in its base plan. If you are buying Hulu only to <strong>Watch Super bowl LVIII</strong>, we will recommend you buy monthly package with ads. It will cost you only <strong>$7.99/month</strong>, which make it’s the cheapest option.</p>
<p>But you also need to check which live channels are offered by Hulu in your locality. Hulu with live transmission includes the TNT, Fox, NFL Network and ESPN which means can get on Sunday afternoon games.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>FuboTV Super Bowl Coverage: </strong></h3>
<p>Some people have asked will Fubo Tv has Super bowl coverage? Yes, Fubo Tv is one of the cheapest options to <strong>watch Super Bowl 2024</strong> as it offers CBS, NBC, FOX &amp; ESPN. Fobu tv has 3 packages:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fubo Pro – <strong>$74.99/month</strong></li>
<li>Fubo Elite – <strong>$84.99/month</strong></li>
<li>Fubo Premium – <strong>$94.99/month</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>NFL Redzone on Fubo tv comes up as sports plus which cost extra <strong>$10.99/month</strong>. You can go with Fubo tv they provide free trial for 7 days. This free trial is available for the new customer. To get this free trial you need to enter credit/debit card at the time of sign up. You will only be charges after the end of free trial period. You can cancel at any time at with in the time period to avoid further subscription charges.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cost to Watch Super Bowl LVIII on Vidgo:</strong></h3>
<p>To <strong>Watch Super bowl 2024 on Vidgo</strong>, you have to buy Vidgo premium subscription for <strong>$20/month</strong> offering NFL redzone &amp; 150+ channels. Vidgo is streaming service offering NFL Regular season to watch on ABC, ESPN &amp; Fox. With Vidgo, Fox Sports is available on vidgo plus deal offering <strong>$49.99</strong> off for first month.</p>
<p>You can compare cost to <strong>Watch NFL Super Bowl LVIII</strong> on streaming services from above table because we want you to choose wisely.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Best Satellite Tv to Stream Super Bowl Sunday 2024</strong></h2>
<p>When it comes to <strong>stream today NFL game</strong> on Satellite Tv, what are options better than Directv &amp; Dish Tv? We will discuss both options in detail. You can see cost comparison of both services to <strong>watch Super Bowl 2024 live NFL Sunday game</strong>.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-table is-style-stripes">
<table class="has-light-green-cyan-background-color has-background">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><strong>Satellite Tv</strong></td>
<td><strong>Price</strong></td>
<td><strong>CBS</strong></td>
<td><strong>Nickelodeon</strong></td>
<td><strong>Fox Sports</strong></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>DIRECTV</td>
<td>$74.99–$154.99/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td>DISH</td>
<td>$79.99–$109.99/mo.</td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
<td><img decoding="async" class="emoji" role="img" draggable="false" src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/svg/2714.svg" alt="&#x2714;" /></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
</figure>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>DirecTv</strong><strong> Super Bowl 2024: </strong></h3>
<p>DirecTv is satellite streaming service which offers local &amp; Cable channels. As <strong>Super bowl Sunday game</strong> will telecast by Fox Sports, you can access Fox Deportes &amp; Fox channel in all plans of DirecTv. It offers 4 plans which viewer can subscribe as per their need which are:</p>
<ul>
<li>DirecTv Entertainment <strong>– $74.99</strong></li>
<li>DirecTv Choice <strong>– $99.99</strong></li>
<li>DirecTv Ultimate <strong>– $109.99</strong></li>
<li>DirecTv Premier <strong>– $154.99</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Cinemax, HBO, Showtime, Starz &amp; MGM+ all are add-ons that you have to buy at <strong>$6 to $11</strong> extra with all plans except DirecTv premier. With <strong>DirecTv access NFL Network to watch Super bowl LVIII</strong> with Ultimate plan, you will find NFL Network on channel 212 of DirecTv.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>NFL Super Bowl Sunday on Dish Tv</strong></h3>
<p>Dish is offering ESPN+ App, CBS, EPSN Channel &amp; NFL Network to <strong>stream Super Bowl LVIII Sunday Game 2024</strong>. IF we compare Dish Tv vs <strong>DirecTv to watch Super bowl 2024</strong>, you can save <strong>$300</strong> with Dish Tv. Just upgrade to Dish Tv with Mastercard &amp; get $300 in prepaid gifts. Dish is offering no surprise price hike, freedom to skip commercial at any time, money back guarantee &amp; 2000 hours of DVR space. Dish tv has 4 plans ranging from <strong>$79.99 to $109.99</strong>.</p>
<p>NFL Network &amp; NFL Redzone to watch Super Bowl on Dish tv comes in Dish Multi Sports pack costs<strong> $13/month</strong> extra. If you don’t have cable tv or any satellite streaming service, we would recommend you to watch Super Bowl Sunday action with VPN at extremely low cost. Details are discussed below.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Watch Super Bowl 2024 live on VPN!</strong></h2>
<p>Beauty of VPN is you can <strong>live stream Super Bowl 2024</strong> from all over the world. Few websites including CBS, NBC Sports &amp; amazon Prime use geolocation tech to Block Non-USA users. VPN unblock those restrictions for you.  Super bowl is the most awaited sport event of United States. Those who don’t have official broadcast available can access to Live action by purchasing VPN’s &amp; then creating a gateway to watch live stream. VPN also offers direct live stream of your favorite sports including <strong>NFL Sunday Super Bowl</strong>. Just buy subscription &amp; you ready to watch wherever you are.</p>
<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-layout-4 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button has-custom-font-size has-medium-font-size"><strong><mark class="has-inline-color has-base-3-color">Get EXPRESS VPN To Watch NFL Live<br />
(49% off + 3 Months Free)<br />
Offering Free Trial</mark></strong></div>
</div>
<p>While choosing VPN’s make sure it has unlimited bandwidth &amp; high internet security features to protect your system from external virus/spam attacks. It should have strict no-logs policy mean VPN is not keeping any of your login details. 3 of the top VPN’s are listed below:</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Nord VPN:</strong></h3>
<p>That VPN provides unlimited bandwidth with 5200+ high speed servers across the world. It also provides you with internet security you want. It is my personal best VPN.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Hotspot Shield:</strong></h3>
<p>It provides free trial without any signup with Credit card. Hotspot shield is good for super bowl streaming with high protection from phishing &amp; malware contents. If you want to use premium features, it comes with 45 days money back guarantee with 7-days free trial.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Express VPN</strong> <strong><mark class="has-inline-color">(Our choice)</mark></strong></h3>
<p>It is one of the best &amp; top use VPN across the world. Express VPN offers servers of over 140+ countries including 30+ cities of U.S. It also provide 256-bit encryption that provides you problem free streaming with 30 days money back guarantee &amp; 7-days free trial for mobile apps. It is most trusted with authentic <strong>live stream Super Bowl 2024</strong> with live Super bowl halftime show.</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Watch Super Bowl LVIII outside USA</strong></h2>
<p>Fans who are residents outside USA or currently in visit to other countries also eager to <strong>watch Super Bowl 2024 live stream outside USA</strong>. No Problem! wherever you are we will tell you the way to access Sunday Night Super Bowl action.</p>
<p>This guide will cover how to <strong>watch Super bowl from Australia</strong>, Europe, Austria, UK &amp; where to <strong>watch Super bowl from Canada</strong> &amp; Mexico. Let’s start!</p>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Watch Super Bowl in Canada</strong></h2>
<p>Viewers from Canada can access Super Bowl Live action on tv channels like TSN, CTV &amp; RDS. You can choose above any streaming service or Satellite tv to watch <mark class="has-inline-color has-accent-color"><strong>Super bowl 58 in Canada</strong></mark>. Most popular option to <strong>stream Superbowl 58</strong> in Canada is DAZN. Just buy the Subscription &amp; you are ready to stream. TSN also comes up with Subscription.</p>
<p>DAZN also you to watch NFL in Italy as well. There are many countries where you can access NFL Sunday night Super Bowl game with DAZN. It offers NFL drafts, Preseason, NFL regular season &amp; Super bowl. It is compatible with every type of streaming device.</p>
<div class="wp-block-buttons is-content-justification-center is-layout-flex wp-container-core-buttons-layout-5 wp-block-buttons-is-layout-flex">
<div class="wp-block-button has-custom-font-size has-medium-font-size"><strong><mark class="has-inline-color has-base-3-color">Get EXPRESS VPN To Watch NFL Live<br />
(49% off + 3 Months Free)<br />
Offering Free Trial</mark></strong></div>
</div>
<p>Cost of DAZN to watch NFL in Canada is <strong>$26.97 CAD/Month</strong> &amp; <strong>$202.36 CAD</strong> for entire year. If you don’t have any subscription we will recommend you to decide wisely between TSN &amp; DAZN. TSN costs you around <strong>$8 USD/month to $80/year</strong>. Both can be accessible on mobile apps.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Super Bowl Live In Australia</strong></h3>
<p>Number of fans email us how they can <strong>watch Live Super Bowl in Australia</strong>? What are the options to watch NFL from Australia? In reply to those queries we have consolidate this guide on <strong>Super bowl 2024 Live in Australia</strong>. DAZN is premium option to <strong>watch Superbowl in Australia</strong>. It unable you to access ESPN &amp; Channel 7 from Australia which are official broadcaster of NFL Super Bowl. Still want the cheapest option, then go With ExpressVPN to enjoy live stream SuperBowl.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Watch SuperBowl 2024 Live in Mexico</strong></h3>
<p>When it comes to watch NFL live in Mexico, we have left with options of many streaming services. Subscription of below service will allow you to live stream Super Bowl 2024 from Mexico.</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Paramount+</strong></li>
<li><strong>NFL+</strong></li>
<li><strong>Sling Tv</strong></li>
<li><strong>Hulu Tv</strong></li>
<li><strong>Peacock Tv</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>Above all platforms will stream Sunday Night Super Bowl from Mexico. To get the plan details, please refer to above headings &amp; choose wisely.</p>
<h3 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Watch NFL From Austria</strong></h3>
<p>Fans from Austria also want to follow live action of Sunday Night Super Bowl 2024. They can stream NFL Super bowl through Cable tv to access local channels to watch Super bowl LVIII. If none of local channel is streaming today NFL game, best option they are left is VPN.</p>
<ol>
<li>Buy the ExpressVPN Subscription</li>
<li>Choose country to watch live from by changing location</li>
<li>Stream with VPN.</li>
</ol>
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Who will Perform at Super Bowl Halftime show?</strong></h2>
<p>Super bowl halftime show is going to rock with sexy performer “Rihanna” who is Barbadian singer.</p>
<p>The post <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu/how-to-watch-super-bowl-2024-live-nfl-sunday-game/">How To Watch Super Bowl 2024 Live NFL Sunday Game</a> appeared first on <a href="https://li.fvtc.edu">Super Bowl LVIII</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://li.fvtc.edu/how-to-watch-super-bowl-2024-live-nfl-sunday-game/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
